本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：侯默   Soomii   红豆包   Iz   Ｊ小糯
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第三集
■
A级牛肉
孩子们  感谢你们到储藏室来帮我忙
Okay, kids, thank you for joining me here in the walk-in.
谢谢你们
Thank you all.
你要我们过来的  所以...
You said we had to, so...
闭嘴
Shush.
我应该把开衫带过来的
I should have brought my cardigan.
我有一件事要宣布
I have an announcement about the restaurant.
这个盒子里的牛肉将要做成
Here in this box is the beef  that will make our--
吉恩  击鼓
Gene, drumroll, please.
好了  可以停了
Okay, enough.
吉恩
Gene.
这个盒子里的牛肉
Here in this box is the beef
将要做成我们店的第十万个汉堡
that will make our 100,000th burger.
我能摸一下吗
Can I touch it?
我也想摸一下
I wanna touch it, too.
我想在脚趾间感受一下
I wanna feel it between my toes. Mmm.
我想在里面放一支炸药
I wanna put a stick of dynamite in it
炸开它
and blow it up!
不行  你们几个都脑抽了么
No. What is wrong with all of you?
除了我其他人不许碰这盒肉
No one's touching this meat but me.
我也有一件事要宣布
I have an announcement, too.
我的胸罩磨得我难受
My bra is chafing me.
那种事不用宣布
That's not a real announcement.
我也有事要宣布
Oh! I have one.
我喜欢
I love...
浩室乐[电子乐的一种]
house music.
好了  我说完了
There! I said it!
我会拿到持枪证的
And I'm going to get my gun license,
一定会的
finally.
恭喜你啊
Oh, congratulations.
难以相信他们让你等了三天
Can't believe they're making you wait three days.
别岔开话题
Stop stealing my thunder!
我找到横幅了
I found the banner!
以前打好的
It's from our old printer.
只要把边上的小洞洞撕下来就行了
You just have to tear off the holes on the side.
我们几年前就该突破十万个汉堡的
We were supposed to hit 100,000 ages ago.
不过以前差得可远着呢
Heh. We were way off.
是啊  重要时刻
Yeah. Big time.
-我能不能  -不行  别动
- Can I just... - No, stop it!
这下可好了
There it is.
-抢啊  -冲啊
- Get it! - Dive!
我的老天
Oh, my God.
你就是第十万个汉堡吗
Are you No. 100,000?
不是
No.
你在生我气吗
Are you mad at me?
没有
No.
汉堡  你真可爱
Oh, burger, you're cute.
你也很可爱哦
You're cute, too.
哪里哪里
Heh. I'm not.
琳达
Whoa whoa. Linda!
电视台来人了
I think the news is here!
我想他们听到了我们店第十万个汉堡的消息
I wonder if they heard about our 100,000th burger!
什么
What?!
开心汉堡店  第十万个汉堡  只要半价哦
你们好  需要帮忙吗
Hi. How are you? Uh, what can I do for you?
你就是鲍勃吗
Are you Bob?
是的
Uh, yeah. I am.
我是兰迪・沃金斯
I'm Randy Watkins,
纪录片制作人
The documentary filmmaker.
然后呢
Okay. Uh...
我们正在制作一部关于牛肉产业的纪录片
We're making a film about the beef industry.
我听说你们就要突破第十万个汉堡了
I heard you were about to hit your 100,000th burger,
我想跟你握个手
and I wanted to shake your hand.
好的
Oh. Yeah. Um...
因为  你的手上沾满献血
Because you, sir, have blood on your hands.
这是番茄酱吗
Eww. Is this ketchup?
这是十万头被屠杀的牛之血
It's the blood of 100,000 slaughtered cows.
你阴我
You ketchuped me.
我们是来逼你面对那些被害者的
We're here to force you to face your victims.
来跟你的肉见个面
Meet your meat.
搞什么
What the hell?
她叫萌莉莎
Her name is Moolissa.
五天后她就要被"处理"了  鲍勃
She's due to be "processed" in five days, Bob,
除非你放过她
Unless you choose to spare her life.
-为  为什么  -没错
- W-why? - That's right.
她的命运由你来决定
You will decide her fate.
牛去牛从倒计时
It's a cow...
开始计时
...ntdown.
我倒要看看当你直视你的汉堡肉时
We'll see what your conscience tells you
你的良心会对你自己说些什么
when you're looking your burger right in the eye.
太荒唐了
Ow! This is ridiculous.
做汉堡又不犯法
It's not a crime to make burgers.
而且我们手上也没有血
There's no blood on our hands!
吵吵什么呢
What's all the yelling about?
原来老爸一直在用死牛做汉堡
Turns out dad's been putting murdered cows in our hamburgers.
你还让我们成了帮凶
And you made us a part of it!
你真让我恶心
You make me sick.
孩子们  别闹了
Kids, please.
快看  一头牛
Oh, look. A cow.
你好呀  金发妞
Hello, Blondie.
糟糕  我把肉弄到你身上了
Oops. I got some meat on you.
活牛顶着死牛  真恶心
Dead cow on live cow. Gross. Heh heh.
天啊
Ohh. God.
琳达  别闹了
Uh, not a good time, Linda.
兰迪  停  别拍了
Randy, stop. Stop filming.
我们不打算出现在你的纪录片里
You know, we're not gonna be in your cow documentary anymore.
你没得选  鲍勃
Well, you don't really have a choice, Bob,
因为没有什么能够阻止我为动物伸张正义
'cause I stop at nothing to expose injustice to animals.
这假发是粘上去的吗
Is that wig glued on?
对  这是让她保持原地不动的唯一方法
Yeah. It's-- it's the only way it would stay put.
这样使她人性化一点
It's to, uh, humanize her.
很可爱
It's cute.
我见过更可爱的
Mmm. I've seen cuter.
老实说  她充其量是四星级
Honestly, she's a four.
兰迪  我  我不知道怎么跟你解释好
Randy, I-- I don't know where to begin.
这头牛都不是母的
You know, this isn't even a female cow.
汉堡肉是阉牛做的  阉牛都是公牛
Beef happens to come from steers, which are male cows.
那  她怎么会有乳房
Then, uh, how do you explain that udder?
好给力的乳房
Whoa. What an udder.
蒂娜  离开那儿
Get away from there, Tina.
那不是乳房
That's, uh, not an udder.
不是吗
Oh, it's not?
兰迪  别听他瞎说
Don't listen to him, Randy.
你去挤挤奶证明给他看
You go ahead and milk that cow.
-好好挤一挤  -我们挤过了
- Milk it good. - Oh, we did.
你怎么挤的  那里可挤不出牛奶
You shouldn't have. Milk doesn't come out of that.
那边的水桶里有挤出来的东西
Something came out of it in that bucket over there.
你是说这桶尿吗
You mean this bucket of urine?
我认得尿  这个就是尿
I know urine, and that's urine.
-吉恩 把它放下  -才不要呢
- Gene, put that down. - No!
它只是闻上去有尿味
Well, it certainly smells like urine,
可能因为那头牛病了
but that's probably because she's sick.
不  她没病
No, she's not sick.
真为你的言行感到耻辱  鲍勃
Sick of your practices, Bob!
好了  我要进去打电话给动物管制中心
Okay. You know, we're gonna go inside and call Animal Control,
那时你们就得滚出这里
and then you'll have to leave.
那么  你是有营业执照的
Okay, so you've got all your permits,
这个店铺你也租下喽
and you're renting this storefront?
-是的  -没错
- Yes. - Oh, yeah.
这头牛打过预防针了吗
And, uh, this cow has had all its shots?
-是的  -对对对对
- Yes. - Sure, sure, sure, sure.
很好  非常好  完工
All right. Well, uh, great. My job is done.
一会见
I'll see you guys later.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
再见  动物管制员
Bye, animal man.
什么
What?
您能否签署一下这份出镜协议
Oh, will you sign a release to be in the movie?
好啊  电影  好啊
Uh, yeah. A movie. Yes.
你会成为大明星的
You're gonna be a star!
-喂喂  -谢谢你  -我说
- Excuse me. - Thank you. - Hello.
-我才是那个叫你来的人  -谢谢
- The person who called you... -Thank you.
你不能让牛站在人行道上  太危险了
You can't have a cow on the sidewalk. It's dangerous.
先生  先生  这里唯一危险的就是
Sir, sir, the only thing dangerous about this cow
这头牛太引人注目了
is how adorable it is. Moo.
把你的手放在这头牛上感受一下
Put your hand on this cow and touch it.
什么
What?
我只知道这能帮得上忙
I just know that that's gonna help you.
摸摸牛
Touch the cow.
摸摸牛  摸摸牛
Touch the cow. Touch the cow.
-我要走了  -摸摸它啊
- I'm walking away. - Touch it.
你就逃避吧  老顽固
Oh, right. Run away, tough guy!
去洗个牛肉澡吧
Yeah! Go take a meat bath!
或是鼓捣鼓捣你们这种人能做出来的事
Or whatever it is you people do!
"M"代表"哞"
Dial "M" for "Mooder",
访问一  镜头一
Interview One, Take One.
非常好
Perfect.
你认为奶牛就该被碾成肉末供人食用吗
Do you think cows should be ground up for food?
就我个人而言  我并不怎么在意
Personally, I don't really care.
但我老爸喜欢把他们碾成肉末
But my father, he loves grinding them up.
这让他干劲十足  亢奋不已
Gives him a rush. Makes him feel alive.
我老爸是一个很坏  很坏的人
Daddy's a bad, bad man.
这部影片有配乐吗
Is this movie gonna have a score?
动人心弦的音乐  你懂的
You know, some music to tug at the heartstrings.
我还没考虑这个呢
I-- I haven't thought about it yet.
听听这个怎么样
Well, check this out.
考虑一下吧
Think about it.
露易丝  你觉得这个像什么
Louise, what does that look like to you?
牛粪  眼力不错  蒂娜  不错
Cow poop. Good eye, Tina, good eye.
不是  我是说它的形状像一个笑脸
No. I mean it's in the shape of a smily face,
就像一个表情符号
like an emoticon.
你觉得奶牛在用它的屁股给你发短信吗
You think the cow is texting you an emoticon with its butt.
真有趣
Very interesting.
也许这头牛正以它所知的唯一方式
Maybe this cow is trying to communicate with us
与我们沟通呢  用它的便便
the only way it knows how, with its feces.
就像奶奶以前那样
Like gram-gram used to do.
妈妈  假设有一个卓越的计划
Mom, let's say you had a brilliant plan,
若要执行
but to execute it,
必须得用牛粪将其写出
you needed to write something using cow poop.
你会怎么做呢
How would you do it?
这是脑筋急转弯吗
Oh. Is this a brainteaser?
做蛋糕时用于做奶油造型的塑料容器
我会用裱花袋
Hmm. I would use a frosting bag.
我们有这个东西吗
Do we have one?
有啊  在餐具室里
Yeah, in the pantry.
我猜对了吗  是不是裱花袋啊
Am I right? Is it a frosting bag?
老妈  我去探个究竟
We'll see, mom.
好了  大功告成
Yeah. Okey-dokey.
孩子们  再见
Bye, kids.
祝你们度过愉快的一天
Have a good day.
你个杀牛凶手
Murderer!
你好啊  兰迪
Oh. Hi, Randy.
它微笑着冲我眨眼呢
Wink with open smile.
这是给我的吗
Is this for me?
肯定是
It has to be.
我该怎么做呢
What should I do?
我该回条短信吗
Should I text back?
借光借光
Coming through.
天啊
Oh, no.
看看他
Oh, look at him.
真可爱  我都饿了
So cute. Makes me hungry.
亲爱的  我现在就想吃汉堡
Honey, I want a burger right now.
你们这些人怎么回事
What's wrong with you people?!
Yeah! What's wrong with you people?!
现在我们来谈一下你的配乐预算吧
Now let's talk about your music budget.
一百万成吗
Is it a million?
这里一个扩音器就够了
We only need one megaphone out here.
你知道你需要什么吗  你需要这个
You know what you need? You need this!
考虑一下吧
Think about it!
我们店好受欢迎哦
Wow. We're mobbed.
谢谢你  纪录片制作人
Thank you, documentary.
琳达  这部片子把我拍成
Linda, the documentary is about me
一个杀牛不眨眼的魔鬼
being an evil cow killer.
杀牛凶手
Murderer!
好了啦  鲍勃
Oh, come on, Bob.
没有负面影响了啦
There's no such thing as bad publicity.
这对我们来说再好不过了
This could be huge for us.
就像性爱录像
Like a sex tape.
Like a sex tape. Uhh.
这是有史以来最好的免费广告
It's the best free advertising we ever had.
我知道  我很悲伤
I know. It's almost sad.
为谁
For who?
我不知道  为那头牛吧
I don't know. The cow.
那头牛将会带着光辉荣耀送到餐桌上
The cow's going out in a blaze of glory.
鲍勃  每个人都完胜
Everybody wins, Bob.
我猜你是对的
I guess you're right.
我是说  这一切看起来是多么的美好
I mean, looks kind of sweet out there--
享受大好时光  会见不同面孔
enjoying the day, meeting people.
你好  奶牛
Hi, cow.
我要吃掉你哦
I'm gonna eat you.
它能听到我们说话吗
Whoa. Can it hear us?
别激动
Easy.
就像沙砾滑过沙漏
Like sands through the hourglass,
我的牙齿就要陷入你的后背
there goes my teeth right into your back.
我老婆就这德行
That's my wife.
鲍鲍  我快要饿死了
Ah, Bobby, I'm frigging starving.
谁会忍心吃掉这头美丽动人的小奶牛呢
Who could eat that beautiful creature?
你真无耻
Shame on you!
你们今天要吃汉堡吗
Are you going to be eating a burger today?
我们连做梦也不曾有吃动物这个念头
We wouldn't dream of eating an animal.
我们在州际公路边开了一家宠物园
We run a petting zoo by the interstate.
名叫"鹅妈妈折扣宠物园"
It's called Mother Goose's Discount Petting Zoo.
宠物马驹  宠物山羊  宠物绵羊
Petting horses, goats, and sheep.
花费不多就能拥有珍贵回忆
Precious memories on the cheap.
它主要是一家动物庇护所
It's basically an animal sanctuary...
那是我们的经济来源
that we make money off of.
没错
Exactly.
牛去牛从倒计时
兰迪  多谢你来采访我们
Oh. Hey, Randy, thanks for the business.
鲍勃  客气什么
Oh, hey, Bob, you're welcome.
我马上要睡觉了  你打算干嘛
Well, I'm gonna go to bed soon. What are you gonna do?
我大概也要去睡觉了  我也是人嘛
Oh, I'll probably go to bed, too, 'cause I'm a person.
拜
Bye.
萌莉莎  小心
M-Moolissa, watch out!
不要啊
No!
带被告
Bring in the accused.
喊什么喊
Yeah, yeah.
露易丝  你要为我辩护吗
Louise, you're defending me?
这个道貌岸然的伪君子受到控告
This so-called MAN stands accused of
他杀害的牛相当于十万块汉堡肉
murdering nearly 100,000 hamburgers worth of cows.
有请萌莉莎出庭作证
I call to the stand, Moolissa.
反对
Objection!
那头牛在装死
That cow's faking his injuries!
我可以证明这一点
And I can prove it.
脑筋转快点
Think fast.
反对无效
Overruled.
萌莉莎  杀害你的人
Moolissa, is the man who killed you
今天出庭了吗
in the courtroom today?
是我
It's me!
就是我
It's me.
我只是个做汉堡的
I just make hamburgers.
从来没想过要当一名杀牛凶手
I never wanted to be a cow killer.
对不起  对不起  对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
睡得够死的了
Whoa. Heavy sleeper.
怎么了
Wh-what happened?
出什么事了  出什么事了
What's the matter? What's the matter?
接着睡你的
Go back to bed.
抱歉  接着睡吧
I'm sorry. Go back to bed.
兰迪
Hey! Randy!
你的牛栓在这里会冻死的
Your cow's gonna freeze to death out here!
兰迪
Randy!
慢点
Shh. Easy.
慢点  退后  退后  退后
Easy. Back up. Back up. Back up.
天啊
Oh, my God.
-我知道  -奶牛居然进来了
- Heh. I know. - It's a cow!
你知道吗  它不会碍事的
You know what? You won't even know it's here.
你就当它不碍事吧
Uh, that was like that already.
我会弄干净的
Definitely clean that.
退后点
Oop. Step back.
这是我做过的最美好的梦
This is the best dream I've ever had!
大家都在地板上嘘嘘喽
Everybody pee on the floor!
谁跟我一起
Who's with me?!
趁热赶紧吃
Okay, eat while it's hot.
好得很  看看这碗麦片对谁有裨益
Well, well, well. Look who's too good for cereal now.
他在取悦这头牛
He's trying to impress the cow.
别犯傻了
Don't be ridiculous.
某人知道如何款待一头半公半母的阉牛
Someone knows how to treat a lady-slash-male steer.
鲍勃  这牛站在这里我感觉很不爽
Bob, I am not comfortable with this situation.
琳  你想我怎么做
Lin, what was I supposed to do?
我做了个疯狂的梦  梦里正在下雨
I had that crazy dream. It was raining.
我也做了个疯狂的梦
Well, I had a crazy dream
但梦里可不会有牛的臀部
that there wouldn't be a cow's A-S-S
在我吃早饭时跟我面前晃来晃去
in my face when I'm eating my breakfast.
我知道那个单词
I know what that spells.
-屁股  -屁股
- Ass.  - Ass.
妈妈
Mom.
-屁股  -住嘴
- Ass. - Stop it.
大家  道别吧
Say goodbye, everybody.
让它回到街边  该待哪待哪
It's going out on the street, where it belongs.
成  成  可以
Of course, okay? Of course.
吃完早饭再说
Right after breakfast.
奶牛无法下楼
Cows can't go down stairs.
-什么  -什么意思
- What? - What's that?
奶牛无法下楼
Cows can't go down stairs.
有这么个说法
That's, like, a thing.
我听说过
I've heard that.
那是个有趣的事实
It's like a fun fact.
鲍鲍
Bobby... Hmm.
奶牛不能下楼吗
Cows can't go down stairs?
最好不是这样
That better not be true.
你们得出什么结论了
Huh. What do you know?
我们只知道你会推上半小时的牛屁股
We know you'll push on a cow's butt for half an hour
也不叫我们帮个忙
without asking for help.
你自己一直占着牛屁股
Gotta have that butt all to yourself.
鲍勃  那头牛怎么了  伙计
Hey, Bob! What's the deal, man?
你对萌莉莎做了什么
What'd you do to Moolissa?
它在楼上  快过来把它弄下去
It's up here! Come get it out!
琳达  它不在这  兰迪
Linda. Uh, it's not up here, Randy.
我老婆发神经
My wife's crazy.
如果他知道我让奶牛进来了
If he knows I brought the cow in,
他就会觉得他赢了
he'll think he won.
他赢了又怎么样
So what if he won?
现在就把这头牛给我弄出去
Get the cow out of the house now.
-别闹了  -你把它给我弄出去
- Stop. - You get it out of the house.
-我正努力...  -快把...
- I'm trying to... - Come get...
这头牛
Oh. Uh, this cow.
这头牛  它在这儿
This cow, yeah, is here.
爸爸  我按你的要求
Dad, I ran that bubble bath
为你和萌莉莎弄好泡泡浴了
for you and Moolissa like you wanted.
泡泡浴
Bubbles!
我是不会和萌莉莎洗澡的  兰迪
I'm not taking a bath with Moolissa, Randy.
还剩下两天
Two days left.
再有两天就能决出是把牛送到屠宰场
Two days to decide to send that cow to slaughter
还是你承认自己是个伪君子  杀牛凶手
or admit you're a hypocrite and a murderer.
好精彩的电影啊
Wow. What a movie.
鲍勃  多精彩的电影啊
Bob, what a movie.
我不是在拍电影  泰迪
It's not my movie, Teddy.
什么  他们拿着摄影机只是跟着你转吗
What, are they just following you around with a camera?
你出镜了  当上大明星
You're in it, you're the star,
却说自己不是在拍电影
but it's not your movie.
伙计们  祝你们好运
Heh. Good luck, guys.
-你能签个出镜协议吗  -没问题
- Will you sign a release? -Sure.
你想要我的亲笔签名吗
Do you want my John K Hancock?
-想  -签哪儿都行吗
- Yeah. - Anywhere?
别  签在横线上
No. On the line here.
我得习惯习惯
Better get used to this, huh?
要在银幕上露脸了  我
Gonna be in the movies. I--
签在横线上就行  签在横线上
Just on the line. Just on the line.
-好的  这么说签哪儿都行吗  -没错
- Right. So anywhere? - Yeah.
不  不  签在写有"请签名"的地方
No! No! Where it says "signature"!
好吧  你叫什么  是签给你吗
Okay, what's your name? Do you want it to you?
泰迪  你在干什么
No, I-- Teddy, what are you doing?!
老鲍  我在给别人签名呢
I'm signing here an autograph, Bob.
好一个幸福的大家庭
One big happy family.
真美好  不是吗  全家人都聚在一起
Isn't this nice, all of us here together?
好个屁
No.
你今晚会用便便给我发短信吗
Are you gonna give me a poop tonight?
跟我聊聊嘛
Talk to me.
鲍勃
Mmm. Bob, huh?
这很好啊  他们蛮合得来的
Well, it's nice. They like each other.
对蒂娜来说是件好事
It's good for Tina.
来嘛  放松  然后...
Come on. Just relax and-- pbbbt!
跟我沟通沟通嘛
It's all about the communicationtion.
你好  萌莉莎
Hi, Moolissa.
怎么愁眉苦脸的
Frowny face?
我对你这么这么好
All I've been is super nice to you,
这就是我得到的回报吗
and this is the thanks I get?
我是那么爱你
I loved you.
我像爱马一样爱你
I loved you like a horse,
马是我最心爱的动物呢
which is my favorite animal.
你知道吗  我们不能这样了
You know what? Let's just stop
免得我们两个会说出让自己后悔的话
before we both say something we'll regret.
比如  "马其实比牛好"
Like that horses are better than cows.
我后悔了
I regret that.
但那是事实
But it's true.
牛去牛从倒计时
牛呢
Where's the cow?
我想你是在问  那只阉牛呢
I believe you mean, "Where's the steer? "
对  它是没有小鸡鸡的哦
Yeah. Don't forget about that penis.
对
Yeah.
萌莉莎
Moolissa?
牛是可以下楼梯的
Ha! Cows can go down stairs.
只需四只羊毛袜
All you need is four wool socks,
一张床垫  和一颗决绝的心
a mattress, and the will to make it happen.
你怎么敢
You didn't.
你的女友现在正拴在外面呢
Your girlfriend is tied up outside.
不
Noooooooooooooooo!
老爸怎么了
What's wrong with dad?
我想他讨厌皮带吧
I think he hates leashes.
家庭内部紧急状况
暂停营业
这不是我的错  兰迪
It's not my fault, Randy.
有人把她偷走了
She was stolen.
我想说  这不是谁的错
I mean, it's no one's fault.
琳达除外
Except for Linda's.
我只是为这个家和家里的地毯
I did what I had to do
做了我该做的
to protect my family and my carpet.
随你怎么说吧  现在我们来看看
Yeah, whatever. So who do we know
谁会偷走一头顶着金色假发的奶牛
that would steal a cow in a blonde wig?
可能是那些变态
Maybe some perverts. Heh heh.
我们昨晚吵架了  我和萌莉莎
We had a fight last night, me and Moolissa.
我真希望有机会向她道歉
I just wish I had a chance to make things right again.
你要是看到
You wouldn't if you heard
她拉给你的便便的话  就不会这么想了
some of the things she was pooping about you.
各位
Hey, guys!
来看看这个
Take a look at this!
花费不多
...on the cheap.
你们就这样把她
You fellas just leave her tied up
栓在这里一整夜吗
here at night all alone?
没错  她不会介意的
Oh, yeah, yeah. She doesn't mind.
我们可以把拖车开过来  是吧亲爱的
We could just back a trailer right up here, honey, huh?
当然  这样就可以给园里添头奶牛了
We sure could, get ourselves a cow.
没错  给园里添头奶牛
Yeah. Get ourselves a cow.
没错  给园里添头
Yeah. Get ourselves a c--
鹅妈妈折扣宠物园
咩咩咩咩黑绵羊
吱吱吱吱核桃钟
这只小猪去过超市
简直是个垃圾场
What a dump.
说得对  她在那儿
Yikes. Hey, there she is.
越过月亮的奶牛[喜出望外的奶牛]
天哪
Oh, dear God.
越过月亮的奶牛
Oh, the cow that jumped over the moon.
看到没  多好啊
See, that's nice.
走吧  我们去把她救出来
Come on. Let's go get her.
我们应该晚上再来
We should come back after dark.
-为什么  -晚上更有戏剧性
- Why? - It's more dramatic.
-蠢死了  -不不不不
- That is stupid. - No, no, no, no.
我几乎现在就能预见  大营救的壮观场景
I can see it now, the big rescue.
我们会用红外线拍摄
We'll shoot the whole thing in infrared.
兰迪  得了吧  用红外线拍摄
Oh, Randy, come-- in infrared?
这太疯狂了
This is nuts.
鲍勃  孩子们这个时间应该上床睡觉
The kids should be in bed, Bob.
可这是红外线拍摄啊  琳  给她看看
It's infrared, Lin. Show her.
酷毙了  酷毙了
Cool! Cool!
你嚷嚷什么
Why are you doing that?
我在打暗号
I'm signaling.
大家准备  匍匐前进
Everybody, serpentine.
出发  我们团结一心
Yes! We're a unit.
爸爸  我要你知道
Dad, you should know
如果出现什么情况
if anything happens,
我随时准备全力出击
I am in full attack mode right now.
我也是  我已经开始想吸血了
Me, too. I'm hungry for blood.
还想吃糖果
And also candy.
孩子们  多谢了
Uh, thanks, kids.
该死  我错过起身的信号了
Damn it. I missed the signal to stand up.
大家  很抱歉
Sorry, everybody.
你让我们很失望
You let down the unit.
我道过歉了
I said I'm sorry.
鲍勃  我们到了  现在怎么做
Bob, we're here. What do we do now?
我们  把门打开
We, uh, uh, open the gate.
没想到这么容易
That was easy.
你们几个在干什么
What do you think you're doing?
吉恩  进攻
Gene, attack!
你们几个小屁孩敢咬我的腿
Ow! Your children are biting my legs!
兰迪  去救萌莉莎  快撤
Randy, get Moolissa. Let's move.
来击个掌  我们做到了
High-five, Bob. We did it.
击掌  兰迪  干得好
High-five, Randy. Nice job.
我是说  要不是孩子们死缠烂咬的话
I mean, we couldn't have done it without the kids
我们也办不成这事儿
biting that woman.
她身上有一股木屑和羊骚味
She tasted like sawdust and goats.
三  二  一
3, 2, 1.
时间到
Beep.
鲍勃  牛去牛从倒计时结束
Bob, the cow-ntdown's over.
决定萌莉莎命运的时刻到了
It's time to decide Moolissa's fate.
说正经的  现在吗
Seriously? Right now?
我们才救下她
We just rescued her.
她本该在屠宰场的  鲍勃
She's due at the slaughterhouse, Bob.
事态将如何发展呢
What's it gonna be?
杀牛凶手
Murderer!
露易丝  给我闭嘴
Louise, shush.
兰迪  能不能暂停一下你那傻缺的摄像机
Randy, can you stop making your stupid movie for one minute
做个正常人行吗
and just be a human being?
我不知道  鲍勃
I don't know, Bob.
你能不能不要做你那恶心的汉堡了
Can you stop making your stupid burgers
做个正常人行吗
for one minute and be a human being?
你现在想让我心生愧疚吗
So now you're gonna guilt-trip me?
这就是我整部影片的主题
That's what the whole movie is about.
兰迪  我还以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends now, Randy,
因为我们一起救下了那头牛
'cause we saved the cow together!
也许行动派兼纪录片制作人就是无法交到朋友
Maybe activists-slash-documentarians can't have friends,
无论他们救下几头牛
no matter how many cows they save!
兰迪  你这么说可太伤人了
Well, that's just sad, Randy!
我知道
I know!
我的天啊  好险好险
Oh, my God. That was close.
要是萌萌有个三长两短的
I don't know what I would do
我可真不知道该...
if anything happened to Moo--
我可没撞她
Ahh. I didn't hit her!
我可没撞她  我踩刹车了
I didn't hit her! I stopped!
她可能没事
She's probably fine.
她死了  一定是牛类心脏病犯了
She's dead. She must have had a cow heart attack.
-不是吧  -不如这样吧
- No. - You know what?
我先把车里的货卸了
Let me get something out of my van real quick.
马上回来
Be right back.
萌莉莎
Moolissa!
上帝啊  不要这样
Oh, my God, no.
不要就这么离我而去
Don't you die on me.
不要离开我  你说话呀
Don't you die. Say something!
露易丝  快看  是一颗心
Louise, look. It's a heart,
一坨心形的便便
A heart-shaped poop.
怎么回事  这可不是我整的
What the hell? I didn't do that.
我要留着它
I'm keeping it.
鲍勃  你还好吗
Bob, you all right?
你的脸色看起来有点惨白
You look a little pale.
我们死翘翘了吗
Are we dead?
我翘了  鲍勃  你只是晕了过去
I'm dead, Bob. You just fainted.
我晕过去了吗
I fainted? Wow.
-真尴尬  -好了
- That's embarrassing. - Okay.
我  我从不晕倒
I'm-- I'm not a fainter.
-没错  我死了  -是啊  对
- Yeah. I'm-- I'm dead. - Right. Yeah.
听着  我想让你为我做件事
But listen, there's something I want you to do for me.
用我的肉体做汉堡
Make burgers out of me.
什么  不行  绝对不行
What?! No. No way.
怎么不行  鲍勃
Yes way, Bob.
听着  自从我遇见你
Look, ever since I met you,
做汉堡这件事就像乌云般笼罩在我心头
making burgers makes me feel like a horrible person.
鲍勃  我是一头阉牛
Bob, I'm a castrated steer.
是啊  我还是个有家室的男人呢
Yeah, I'm a married man.
讽刺自己像阉牛一样没鸡鸡
开玩笑啦
Yeah, I'm kid--
其实我们是一样的  对吧
Same thing, right?
是啊   还是好好想一想吧
Yeah. Think about it, though.
我是一头牛  你知道的
I'm a cow, you know?
我们不是野种马  也不是座头鲸
We're not wild stallions or humpback whales,
但这不能让我们甘于平凡
But we wanna feel special, too.
反正我是不甘
I do, anyway.
你让我变得更美好
You turn me into something amazing.
等一下  这是我的潜意识在跟我说
Wait. Isn't this my subconscious
我想听的话吧
telling me what I want to hear?
才不是呢
Hey, no.
告诉你把  没错  实际上还真是
You know what? Yes, it is, actually.
很管用  继续说
Well, it's working. Keep talking.
吻我
Kiss me.
不  我做不到
No. I can't do that.
你能的  你也想这么做
You can, and you want to.
好吧
Okay.
小小地亲一口  谁让我欠你呢
One quick one because I owe you.
还是不要了吧  也许我  我们不应该
Uh, maybe not. Maybe I-- we shouldn't.
什么不应该  来嘛
Oh, we should, absolutely.
我的上帝  我在做什么
Oh, my God. What am I doing?
你要做什么
What are you doing?
我要亲吻一头牛
I'm about to kiss a cow.
没错
Yeah.
鲍鲍  你还好吗
Bobby, are you okay?
老爸那张嘴撅来撅去的是在干嘛
What's dad doing with his mouth?
好像在接吻呢
Looks like he's kissing.
太丢人了
Well, this is awkward.
快来人在这里盖张毯子
Somebody put a blanket over it.
真美味啊
Tastes so good.
好了好了  你们都给我进去  马上
Okay. All right. Kids inside! Now!
在遇到萌莉莎之前
Before Moolissa,
我总说  不过是牛肉罢了
I used to say it's just beef.
我大错特错  错得离谱
I couldn't have been more wrong.
奶牛是一种
Cows are living creatures
长有美丽长发和温顺褐眼的动物
with beautiful hair and soft brown eyes,
还有柔软的双唇
soft mouths...
同时  它们也是肉牛
And also they are beef.
他们就是一具皮囊
They're the full package.
我这样说虚伪吗
Does that make me a hypocrite to say that?
-虚伪  -才不呢  兰迪
- Yes. - No, it doesn't, Randy.
就算虚伪  我也能泰然自若
Or if it does, I can live with that.
现在我来展示一下我们第十万个汉堡
I present our 100,000th burger.
第十万个汉堡
100,000th burger!
好棒哦
All right!
行了  把横幅打出来
Right. Undo the banner.
开心汉堡店  突破十万  好棒
Bob's burger, 100,000! All right!
给力哦
Hooray!
展示横幅
Do the banner.
横幅在这  横幅来啦
Here's the banner! Here comes the banner!
我谦虚地称其为"安息汉堡"
I humbly call this the rest in peas burger.
因为它是用甜豆和胡萝卜做的
Because it, uh, comes with snap peas and carrots.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
好了  各位出席葬礼的朋友
All right, funeral people,
来狂欢吧
It's time to party!